so many choices but will only settle for
the one hello and welcome to the next
top advisor
[Music]
slowly but surely but steady at happy
let's go so to my right
is none other than mistina santos you
should know that she's a very meticulous
woman
i'm so excited joseph
is that when it comes to my finances
so good luck to everyone
yes and to my left
we've got the one and only mrs sandy
cruz a successful mommy of three
nagagui
family thank you for the wonderful
introduction
in
super excited to be here and to listen
to what our participants have to say
thank you very much tina and sandy well
you've met the judges now it's time to
meet the talents who will attempt to
grab our attention and be the next top
advisor
first up we've got financial advisor
number one
ben camacho he claims that he already
knows the ins and outs of managing your
finances
if you give him your trust
he'll give you
the right policies
that's what he said
right ben
you're up
ben camacho
what would you do if your client is
presented with overwhelming product
information if i'm presenting the client
hard to grasp information i'll tell them
to make use of their phone to jot down
notes and have a copy close by so that
they can easily check when they need to
remember the terms
guys i mean let's embrace the digital
age
uh mr ben what would you offer the
client if they are celebrating their
policy anniversary here's an idea
instead of giving her something
i'll promise her that in two years she
can double her money and get more than
what you bargained for
just like that
i don't think you gave us a concrete
answer
[Music]
it's time to move along so let's all
welcome financial advisor number two
carla bautista
carla is 32 years old and she's known to
be the social butterfly of her barcada
friendlina
but will her ideas
work with our given scenarios
you can do this carla it's your turn
start them yeah when you're just
starting to invest in your future
what policy do you think uh would be
best to avail first
as a good financial advisor
i believe that any investment for your
future
is a good investment
miscarlo bautista
a common misconception about insurance
and investment
is that
it would cost you an arm
and a leg
how would you
explain this to your client
well i know investing in your future
feels like it costs more than the
protection it gives
but for me
i believe
that
as long as you do your best
you can do it
can i be honest
i'm sorry but
it's a no for now
and with that we are down to the last
round let's hear it from financial
advisor number three
mark de la cruz
mark who is 25 years old has been
managing his own money since he was a
child
he says that he got a lot of guidance
from his parents
he is very passionate and professional
about his job
but
he never
oversteps and only gives expert advice
on financial matters
the chosen one
let's find out
mark say i've chosen you as my financial
advisor once i've signed the policy and
all what's next for you and i my idea
for this one is the concept of
maintaining a good client advisor
relationship
even after the sale i will continue to
be your financial partner i will
continue to understand your financial
needs and goals i will never leave you
hanging and will always be available if
you have any issues or concerns about
your policy hindi hindi
what makes your financial ideas unique
compared to others the good thing about
giving me your trust is that i've got
plans for your future that you never
knew you needed you can also choose from
different plans that will fit your
lifestyle perfectly i will also try to
anticipate your needs by listening to
you more
happiness and concerns
that i will be with you wherever you are
in your journey at a pressure because
the choice will always be up to you
very eloquent random empathy
yeah i mean it was really really great
so for that
it's a yes for me
[Music]
we've come to a decision
and we chose a financial advisor that we
felt
more comfortable and confident in we
really made sure
reliable empathetic and genuine
someone you can call and go to in times
with me
aspirational and make sure the hata
aspects of huemo are managed well
thank you so
so much tina and sandy
this is it
the next top advisor is
drum roll please
mark de la cruz
wow thank you judges so abram thank jose
soborta indico bb
because you chose me starting today i
will help make your everyday better
that is it
for today everyone keep an eye out for
more episodes and don't forget to
subscribe to the manulife youtube
channel so you never miss out i guess
with manulife you can make every day
better
[Music]
thank you for watching the next top
advisor this has been joseph mendoza
i'll see you next time
[Music]
you